(Bernadette:)and one thing leads to another.
(Amy:)I do know what that's like.
I really do.
(Leonard:)I'm not seeing anyone
(Leonard:)using liquid helium
vortices like this.
(Howard:)I'm not finding
anything either.
That's a good sign.
(Sheldon:)Oh, wait, I found something.
(Howard:)Damn. What is it?
(Sheldon:)This video.
The baby panda sneezes,
(Sheldon:)and the mama panda
gets so scared.
(Leonard:)Can you focus
on what we're talking about?
(Penny:)All right.
(Sheldon:)Look, now,
this may be the rum talking,
(Sheldon:)but as long as the unpinning
rate of the vortices
(Sheldon:)is kept within 1.1 and 1.3,
(Sheldon:)the Magnus force issue
should be negligible.
(Raj:)Even drunk, he's still smarter
than all of us.
(Sheldon:)And stronger.
Yeah. Who wants to see me
beat up the bartender?
(Leonard:)I'd enjoy that.
(Sheldon:)Nah, she's a good kid.
(Howard:)If this is a viable thing,
we could get a patent